million is 10,000 dollars Well, more than 12
лям это 10.000 долларов Да ну поболее 12
years, but how Well, why do you owe such
лет а как Ну за что вы должны такие
amounts, overdue loans,
суммы просроченные кредиты
utilities, and utilities there, in
коммуналка та коммуналка там уже у вас в
Russia, they’re already small Well, I don’t know, you have to
России маленькая Ну это не знаю это надо
live in a communal apartment for 100 years to
100 лет жить в коммуналке чтобы такую
get that amount No, you don’t see how it turned out for us,
сумму набрать нене не видишь как у нас
that is, for us, if you don’t
получилось то есть у нас если ты не
pay your loans, 50% of your
платишь по кредитам у тебя 50% из
salary is deducted
зарплаты вычитают
for the second 50%, you have to support your family,
на вторые 50% тебе надо содержать семью
you have to eat something,
тебе надо что-то кушать во что-то
wear something And you practically don’t have anything
одеваться И у тебя уже практически не
left to pay for
остаётся заплатить за коммунальные
utilities Opa That’s it, I understand everything here
услуги Опа Всё я тут всё я
And you didn’t leak it, no, and I was smoking, I was hanging out
понял А вы не слили нет а я курил я
on his toilet, there was wi-fi,
завис у него на унитазе wi-fi
what did I think, you had wi-fi on the toilet,
был чего я думал у вас на унитазе wi-fi
because the Wi-Fi
был потому что
disappeared, I say wi-fi, I thought you had it
пропало что Wi говорю wi-fi думал у тебя
on the toilet What are you talking about,
на унитазе О чём общаешься
who asks what, then we talk Listen,
кто что спросит по то мы общаемся Слушай
what do you think, Why is Russia at war with
как ты считаешь Почему Россия воюет с
Ukraine
Украиной
simpler or more complicated answer more complicated more
попроще или посложнее ответи посложнее
complicated And you will listen Well,
сложнее А ты будешь слушать
even now with my wife on this
Да ну вот даже сейчас с супругой на эту
topic we talked about what is happening that
тему общались про что происходит то что
negotiations there are not negotiations Well,
там переговоры не переговоры Ну
initially, in general, initially, as I
изначально вот вообще изначально как я
think, my case
считаю моё су
about the lease of Crimean, these ports, everything
о аренде Крымских вот этих портов всего
else, and they wanted to give it to NATO that
остального и хотели отдать НАТО что
NATO was based instead of the Black Sea
базировалось НАТО вместо Черноморского
Fleet of the Russian
флота Российской
Federation, it initially
Федерации изначально
began I think with
началось Я думаю с
this Well, again, I was
этого Ну опять же году мне было
20 years old, I understand well And why is it fighting because they
20 льно понимаю А почему воюет потому
wanted to join
что захотели в
NATO
НАТО
first, it was necessary to fight To
первых было воевать надо было
negotiate and who is to blame for this
Договариваться а кто виноват в этой
war and
войне а
so the Russian Federation started the war there is
так войну начала Российская Федерация
nothing to
нечего тут
think about here I think until they
думать Я считаю пока не
attacked history that starting with Rus' Russia
напали история что начиная с Руси России
USSR RSFSR until they jerked do not jerk
СССР РСФСР пока они дёрнули не дёргаться
[music]
[музыка]
ourselves somehow like this is mine And how are your
самим как-то вот моё такое А как у вас
people tired of this
люди устали уже от этой
war already Yes, probably just like you, everyone is
войны Да так же наверное как и у вас все
tired Nothing good people say how
устали Ничего хорошего люди говорят как
it should end and when a
она должна закончиться и когда
difficult
сложный
question That's exactly right specifically like this they
вопрос Вот именно вот прямо конкретно
discussed me even in my
так вот меня обсуждали даже вот в моём
team where I work there in the family we did
коллективе где я работаю там в семью мы
not discuss how and
не обсуждали как и
what  One hope is that it should somehow
чего Одна надежда что она должна как-то
end,
закончиться
you know, in a good way, then everything is clear, well,
знаешь по-хорошему то всё понятно что ну
we are to blame and we need to back off, all the reparations and
виноваты мы и надо там всё репарации и
everything
всё
else, but
прочее отстать но
then again, we are not in power, there are
опять же мы не у власти у власти там
other people in power and they have their own goals, what do they
другие люди и у них свои цели чего они
want to
хотят
achieve? And what are the goals of this war,
добиться А какие цели этой войны
then, how
тогда как
official or not real, I do
там официальную или как не реальную
n’t
реа не
know?
знаю Усть
For God’s sake, why Netto is necessary so that they don’t go there?
ради Бога Почему Нетто надо чтобы не шли
Why not? Let it be so, as for me, no
е Почему нет Пускай как вот по мне от
one will get worse from this, you are a closer
этого хуже никому не станет тебя ближе
partner in trade in everything else,
партнёр по торговле по всему остальному
here you are again, the EU Finland is the border of
вот те тя опять же ЕС Финляндия граница
Russia, so trade what you want,
России вот торгуй что хочешь
do what exactly about security, again,
делай что именно по безопасность опять
We never, well, Russians do not surrender
же Мы никогда не ну Русские не сдаются
until they
пока не
attack, until they attack, there is nothing to twitch about.
нападут пока не нападут дёргаться нечего
Listen, I’m fine, here’s the question, because of
Слушай я хорошо вот такой вопрос из-за
this war, has your life become better, has it
этой войны вам лучше стало жить хуже
changed, it hasn’t
изменилось не
changed, worse. Listen, as for me, nothing has
изменилось Вот слушай как по мне ничего
changed now, and the spouses
не поменялось сейчас жи супруги
are asking, what has made your
спрашивают что ж тебе от войны стало
life worse or harder because of the war, something has changed for us,
жить хуже или тяжелее у нас поменяло
specifically in the financial sense, only Well,
что-то именно в финансовом плане
that is, in the financial sense. Well, financially,
толь Ну то есть в финансовом Ну
Yes.  nothing on the planet and the fact that here is a
финансовых Да плане ничего а то что вот
set of finances Yes, we were not so
набо финансова Да мы как были ни так
remained
остались
if on Dolgov there
если у на Долгов не
was no yes well that is what you see
было да ну то есть то что видишь
acquaintances I have there and Odnoklassnik
знакомых у меня же там и Одноклассник
died and there is a neighbor someone else Well that's
погиб и там сосед ещё кто-то Ну вот
exactly people people I feel sorry for I also have a
именно люди людей жалко У меня тоже да
lot of acquaintances from Russia there was such Sanya
знакомых из России много был такой Саня
Prokhorov And you La this is rumors not Lithuania
Прохоров А у тебя Ла это молвы не Литвы
Lithuania I am from Lithuania Lithuania
Литвы Я из Литвы Литвы
This is why Moldovan
Это почему молдавский
thought I apologize I do not have it I have I had a
подумал извиняюсь Я не
classmate he was from
оть у меня У меня одноклассник был он из
Lithuania went then he himself Russian studied
Литвы поехал потом он сам русский учился
in Lithuania and then went to Russia received
в Литве а потом Поехал в Россию получил
citizenship went to his own place last year
гражданство поехал на сво в прошлом году
and in short lived a week on his own place and
и короче неделю прожил на ссво и
died you know honestly that's not this think I
умер знаешь честно вот не этот подумай я
myself broke through a couple of times you know because of
пару раз сам прорывался именно знаешь
what because of financial
из-за чего из-за финансовых
problems What exactly do you just
проблем Что именно ты же только
sign a contract and you immediately get money
подписываешь контракт тебе сразу бабки
dripping Yeah that you will solve the issues here
капают Угу что ты решишь вопросы здесь
everything and there it's just a matter of
все а там уж как
luck there is a neighbor from the first
повезёт есть вот вот сосед с первого
floor he is already there well from the very beginning he
этажа он уже там ну с самого начала он
got a cook roughly speaking
попал поваром грубо говоря
Oh no he got a cook Yes he cooks there
О нет он попал пова Да он готовит там
somewhere Near Lugansk he gets the
где-то Под Луганском зарплату получает
same salary, a big salary, sorry, there's
самую зарплата большая Извини там с
a little over a thousand, well, a thousand bucks,
лишним с лишни тысяч ну штуки баксов
roughly speaking, he gets them, he
грубо говоря он получает их он поваром
works as a cook, he doesn't go into battle, nothing, but you
работает в бой не ходит ничего но ты
can get in, like you said, that you'll
можешь попасть так как ты сказал что ты
arrive first
приедешь первую же
[music]
[музыка]
our guys are taking everyone out, yeah, yeah, yeah, what's the big deal,
неде всех убирают наши же
yeah, that's the guy there, that guy Well, they've been there since the very beginning of the war,
дядька Ну что они с самого начала войны
and it seems like the order was given to dump them And
и вроде как пошла команда и их сливать А
what, no idea You know yourself Well, they do
что без понятия Сам же знаешь Ну оттуда
n't call from there and they don't tell you much detail
не звонят и сильно подробно не
Well, they call, they call,
рассказывают Ну звонят звонят
of course, from the front lines, we don't know the details, we're waiting for those
конечно с передовой подробности не знаем
who have been fighting for 3 years,
ждём пока типа тех кто 3 года уже воюет
that they're just being slaughtered and that's it, yeah, it's
что пускают на мясо просто и всё да
their half, yeah, yeah, it's their regiment
именно их пол дадада именно вот их полк
where they serve, there's no guy,
где вот служит там не дядька погибли
two died, they disappeared, well, like today on
двое пропали ну как вот сегодня в
the news, I haven't seen this guy with the
новостях не видал этот с
flag, yeah That's exactly what's on the
флагом да Вот именно вот что за на
tanks of the region with the Victory flags across a
танках области с флагами Победы по
minefield Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah And we
минному полю Да да да вот и вот А мы вот
heard this news a long time ago  already days ago on
эту новость услышали ещ сколько уже дней
Neda exactly a week exactly yes what have you
по Неде точно неделю точно да что
heard that like this How will they drain
слышали что вот вроде Как сливать будут
those who have served for a long time And
тех кто давно служит А
why the question is of course
зачем вопрос конечно
interesting I can't understand I don't know I'm
интересный Я не могу понять Я не знаю я
afraid to even guess I can't even guess Well
боюсь я даже не могу предположить Ну
what could there be with her
какие могут быть при ею
army maybe problems with the head why would she
армию может проблемы с башкой чего она
come to me for buckwheat for Ta I don't know
меня за гречку пришла бы за Та не знаю
maybe she didn't eat
можно она не жрала
Sorry dog ​​Over here all happy with
Извини собака Вон тут вся довольная у
us walking Or maybe it could be that the
нас ходит А може может такое быть что
money for salaries just ran out and in
просто бабки на зарплату закончились и
short people just need to be disposed of
надо короче людей просто утилизировать
I doubt it if you understand If they raise
сомневаюсь если понимаешь Если повышают
until now they
до сих пор
raise for one signature because it's the
повышают за одно подписание пото что
same Kazan gives a million You just sign a million
тоже самое Казань ляма дают Ты только
you all at once Just
Подпиши ляма те сразу всё Вот ты только
sign with us in Yaroslavl how much is there in
Подпиши у нас по ярославски сколько там
my opinion something around two yes something
по-моему что-то около двух да что-то
around d l Do I understand correctly that you
около д л я правильно понимаю что вы
understand that To hell with this war but they
понимаете что Нафиг это война но
dug around because of financial difficulties to
порылись изза материальных трудности
go to war to pay off
пойти на войну чтобы закрыть
debts specifically I had such an idea
долги конкретно у меня была мысль такая
Yes specifically I had And what does my wife think about this
Да конкретно у меня А что жена про это
that she needs alive and healthy
думает что ей нужен живой и и здоровый
here that we with ours  financial
здесь что мы со своими финансовыми
difficulties we'll cope little by little
трудностями справимся потихонечку
somehow
как-нибудь
and it's not worth going to war
и не стоит оно того чтобы идти на войну
And what kind of debts do you have and what
А какого характера у вас долги и какая
amount do you have
сумма сколько у на
Well, somewhere around probably half a million
Ну где-то около наверное полумиллиона
all together It seems to me
всё вместе Мне кажется
00 600000 according to I se if you count my lies I have se
00 600000 по я се если считать мои лги у
there closer to 5 definitely have
меня там се секун ближе 5 точно есть
plus your
плюс твои
credit cards million here million
кти лям вот лям
Wait Stop million this million this 10,000
Подожди Стоп лям это лям это 10.000
dollars yes Well
долларов да
more than 12 years and how Well why do you
Ну поболее 12 лет а как Ну за что вы
owe such
должны такие
amounts overdue loans
суммы просроченные кредиты
utilities that utilities there are already small in your
коммуналка та коммуналка там уже у вас в
Russia Well I don't know it's 100
России маленькая Ну это не знаю она 100
years to live in a communal apartment to have such an amount
лет жить в коммуналке чтобы такую сумму
Nara no you don't see how it turned out for us that
Нара не не видишь как у нас получилось
is with us if you don't pay your
то есть у нас если ты не платишь по
loans 50% of your salary is deducted
кредитам у тебя 50% из зарплаты вычитают
for the second 50% you need to support your family
на вторые 50% тебе надо содержать семью
you need to eat something something to
тебе надо что-то кушать во что-то
wear And you practically have nothing
одеваться И у тебя уже практически не
left to pay for
остаётся заплатить за коммунальные
utilities in the winter you understand heating  no
услуги зимой сам понимаешь отопление не
heating there a little more Wait Stop well
отопление там чуть-чуть поболе Подожди
these debts How long have they been hanging on you for
Стоп ну эти долги Сколько уже на вас
two or three years probably
висят уже года два-три наверно года
two or three years I just don't understand how you can
два-три Я просто не понимаю как можно на
collect on utilities it's not just
коммуналке набрать видно не только
utilities And what are you overdue
коммуналка А за что вы там просроченные
loans for there what did you take
кредиты на что вы брали
loans for in for example
кредиты в например
Ache took out a loan lived ate walked
Аче брали кредит жили жрали гуляли
phones young when you were wait well this is
телефоны молодые когда были подожди ну
10,000 dollars this is damn well this is for
это 10.000 долларов это блин ну
me loans you know even
это у меня-то кредиты сам зна даже
there the wife helped a friend
там супруга помогала подруге квартиру
buy an apartment add money to buy an
купить добави е денег на покуп
apartment the wife died that is and the
квартиры у супруги умерла то есть а
debts remained on the wife that is there
долги остались на жене то есть там не
was no without a subscription without everything without Well once again I did
было ни без подписки без всего без Ну
n't understand the question how she
ещё раз не понял вопрос как
helped Well that is her friend wanted to
помогала Ну то есть у неё подруга хотела
buy an apartment she didn't have enough money
взять квартиру ей не хватала суммы
asked her friend take out a loan I'll give it to you
попросила подругу возьми кредит я тебе
yes that is she helped gave and in the
отдам да то есть помогала давала и в
end she died wait did I
итоге вот умерла подожди я правильно
understand correctly that the friend wanted to buy herself an
понял что подруга себе хотела купить
apartment and asked your wife so that the wife would
хату и попросила вашу жену чтобы жена
take out a loan for money and give it to her yes yes yes
взяла в кредит бабки и дала ей да да да
business scheme And why  it was for your wife
бизнес схема А зачем это вашей жене
Well, my friend, how is she? Explain, well,
было Ну подруга как она Объясни а ну
let me listen to my wife, how is your
дайте я послушаю жену как Как зовут
wife's name Ksenia Ksenia,
жену Ксения Ксения
and what motivated you to take out a loan
а чем вы мотивировали что взять кредит
for your
за
friend, ses, I'll clarify that Ksenia can't
подругу сес уточню что Ксения тебя не
hear you, I'll rephrase, well, that is, I'll repeat
слышит я перефрази ну то есть повторю
Ksyusha, what motivated you to take this
Ксюш ты чем мотивировала чтобы взять эти
money to buy an apartment? That is,
деньги на покупку квартиры То есть
motivation, how is it? Let's start with the fact
мотивация как это давай начнём с того
that it wasn't a purchase of an apartment. And
что это была не покупка квартиры А на
what did she buy the apartment for? With maternity
что вообще-то квартиру Она купила На мат
capital. And what did
капитал А на что
she pay off the debts with? I had 100 and 30. I
30 она закрывала долги
didn't motivate her in any way. I just
я я ничем не мотивировала я просто
wanted to help her. I knew who I was taking it from. I knew
хотела ей помочь Я знала кому я беру я
what her attitude was to money and
знала какое у не отношение к деньгам и
debts. I knew that she would give it back. It's
долгам Я знала что она будет отдавать
just that no one knew that it would
Просто никто не знал что вот так
turn out like this, that she
получится что она
always
умт всегда
gave it back and would be left penniless, but with money. Oh,
отдавала остаться без копейки но деньги
in short, yes, that is, she did
О В общем короче да то есть она этот
n't even take this apartment, but a room in a
взяла даже не квартиру а комнату в
communal apartment, with this money, with maternity
коммуналке на эти деньги на манский
capital, but she had debts before that,
капитал но у неё до этого оставались
and so her wife helped her so that she would
долги и вот супруга ей помогла чтобы она
pay them off.  debts but for debts She
рассчиталась долгами но за долги Она
always paid that is Well no one
всегда рассчитывалась то есть Ну никто
expected that it was the Friend that would
не ожидал что именно Подруга это
die wait am I right I
умрёт подожди я правильно я правильно
understand correctly I understand correctly that your
понимаю я правильно понимаю что ваша
wife uh borrowed money so that the Friend could
жена э взяла деньги в долг чтобы подруга
pay off her debts
рассчиталась со своими долгами
Yes and why couldn't the Friend take out a
Да а почему подруга не могла взять
loan
кредит
I think because they didn't give it to her because she
я так думаю пото что ей уже не давали
was already up to her
пото что уже в долгах была как в
ears in debt So what if they didn't
шелках Так а как же смотри если ей не
give it to her because she was up to her
давали потому что она в долгах была как
ears in debt How did your wife plan that
в шелках Как ваша жена планировала что
she would
она ей
give it back to her I would say even I have such a view of the
отдаст я так скажу даже у меня такой
ban of a
бан
person I will always give it to a person And
е человека я человеку всегда отдам А
banks Well they will be patient
банки Ну потерпят
I think they will take it anyway Yes they will take it
вот я думаю они всё равно возьмут Да они
anyway there they have their own right they
всё равно там правильно гово своё
will take it from them there and insurance and so on and
возьмут у них там и страховки и и прочее
human relations are different That is
а человеческие отношения - это другое То
again here uh the same Friend that is
есть опять же вот э же подруга то есть
when the spouse took it from her Well she gave her
она когда супруга взяла ей Ну дала ей
money that is she gave there well for six months
деньги то есть она давала там ну полгода
she gave it But even more Yes but
она отдавала Но даже больше Да но вот
such a tragedy happened that she died
случилась такая трагедия что она умерла
but the debt hung on us That's on us that there
но долг повис Да вот на нас то что там
was no  nothing is insured Yes, it's stupid,
не было не застраховано ничего Да глупо
but Well, yes,
но Ну так есть
and why did she
а она от чего
die from
умерла от
gravity, fell out of the window, right,
гравитации выпала из окна правильно
gravity Can you explain in more detail
гравитации А можете детальнее объяснить
This is an interesting
Это интересный
story I can't, did she
сюжет не могу
jump out or was she
она выбросилась или её
thrown out, the second
выбросили второй
option is that her other creditors
вариант так то есть её другие кредиторы
came somewhere and demanded something from her No,
где-то пришли и требовали от неё что-то
no,
Да нет
tragic Well, explain to me, I'm just
трагических Ну объясни мне просто
interested in this
интересно уже этот
story Well, it so happened that she was sitting
сюжет Ну так получилось что вот сидела
on the windowsill and fell out of the window, she didn't fall, she was thrown out Well, they threw her out Well,
на подоконнике и упала в окно не упала
who threw her out, under what circumstances
кто выбросил при каких обстоятельствах
Let the wife tell the
Пусть жена расскажет
story The wife doesn't want to tell
историю жена не хочет рассказывать
Kristina Please tell me, tell me
Кристина расскажите пожалуйста скажите
that I really ask Kristina to tell the
что я очень прошу Кристину рассказать
story Well, firstly, Ksenia, and secondly,
историю Ну во-первых Ксения и во-вторых
she can't hear you Ksenia, what I'm
она вас не слышит Ксения то что я же
saying Tell her, I really ask you, we
говорю Передайте ей я очень прошу
don't want
не хотим
Please, can you give me an earphone for a
Пожалуйста можете наушник сени дать на
minute, you have two of them, what do you have,
минуту у вас их два что у вас два
one is dead, I'll give it to Ksenia later, that's
наушника один разряженный я вот потом
all, you can give it to her for a minute I want to
всё можете ксени на минутку дать Я хочу
ask her to
вот ей попросить чтобы она историю
tell the story, she doesn't want to, she's busy Okay,
рассказала она не хочет она занята Ладно
ask on my behalf that I want to
попросите от моего имени что я хочу
hear this story, let her  will tell
услышать эту историю пусть она расскажет
to I understand that they want to talk to me
к Я так понимаю со мной хотят
About what Well how did it happen About what What Who
пообщаться О чём Ну как так получилось О
and who from what Her out the
чём что Что кто и кто из чего её в
window I told you all this 10 times
окно Я же тебе всё это 10 раз рассказал
Well how to
Ну как правильно
say it correctly Well the guy with whom she started
сказать Ну мужик с которым она начала
talking Yes the guy with whom she was there
общаться Да мужик с которым она там была
love was love love [ __ ] understand what's wrong with his
любовь была любовь лю хуй пойми что с
head Narco like well like Narco
башкой Нарко вроде как бы ну вроде Нарко
but he still yes also not
но он всё да тоже его не
his azl he in short well in short You see there was a
его азл он короче ну короче Вот видишь
friend found herself a
была подруга нашла себе мальчика
bad boy And the boy her out the window and he
нехорошего А мальчик её в окно а сам
overdosed That's the situation And this boy She had
передоз Вот такая ситу А этот мальчик У
before she took out the loan
неё был до того как она вы кредит взяли
or after it was
или после
n't it in the new party yes Well
не это же в новой партек было да
where She took an apartment com this is a
Ну где Вот она квартиру взяла ком это
dormitory Well that is he was new she had
общежити Ну то есть он новый был она же
n't talked to him before
с ним до этого не общалась
and they met they lived in the same
и познакомились они жили в одном
dormitory further away she a little that's how she
общежитии подальше она чуть-чуть это как
moved there there
туда переехала там
and that is your wife helped took out a
и то есть ваша жена помогла взяла
loan she paid off her
кредит она рассчиталась со своими
debts there some lived in this
долгами там какими-то жила в этой
apartment who bought a
квартире кото купила
drink introduced to this
напи познакомила с этим
Narco No  wow story And wait since
Нарко Не [__] история А подожди раз
maternity capital means she had children
мат капитал значит у неё были дети
How many children did she have
Сколько детей у неё
two how
было двое по сколько им
old are they T Le 15 probably already yes
лет сколько Т Ле 15 наверное уже да
And Sophie probably still well in short at that
А софик наверно ещё ну короче на тот
time it turns out that by the age of two Well at
момент получается что к двум годам Ну на
that time it turns out that Styopka was 14 years old Olya is six months and a
тот момент получается стёпки лет 14 Оли
kopeck no Sophie she should have been
полгода с копейко нет Софи ей ей
almost a year old because she
практически год должен был потому что ей
should have been in the summer She died in the summer
летом должно было Она же умерла летом
in a month or two that was not it I
через месяц или через два не это было Я
forgot June Yeah and in August the first of
у забыла июнь Угу а в августе перво
August is Sonya's birthday That is,
августа у соньки день рождения То есть
it was before the year Well yes in short yes it turns
это до года было Ну да короче да
out the eldest is 14 and the youngest is
получается старшему 14 а младшей годик
almost a year old I understood that is, it is a year old not
почти понял то есть это ко годик не
now but then it was when she fell out Well well
сейчас а тогда было когда она выпала Да
at that time yes Well that is 2 years
ну на момент да Ну это то есть 2 года
ago I understood correctly I understand that the
назад я понял я правильно понимаю что
mother gave birth to a child right there from an
мама это родила ребёнка тут же от
unknown man or a well-
неизвестного мужика или
known well-known And where is that man
известный известный А где мужик тот
Alki Yes he has it
альки Да у него
yes yes and what is he doing with him now I know that since she
же да да а он сечас с ним что с знаю я
broke up with him and that's it yes that is in
что она как с ним рассталась так и всё
short the nominal dad sent him
короче номинальный папа послала его
That is, it turns out she gave birth  from this
То есть получается она родила от этого
Valka received maternity capital bought a
вальки получила маткапитал купила
room in a
комнату в
dormitory your wife took money for her
общежитии ваша жена взяла для неё бабки
so that she would pay off her debts and
чтобы она закрыла свои долги какие-то А
then she had a year old child and she
дальше у неё там ребёнку год а она с
got into trouble with someone yeah Well something like that yeah it's
каким-то нарвалась да Ну типа того
fun yeah I myself understand what was going on
да весело да я ВС сам понимаю что вело
It's like
Это как
Interesting and everything was fine with her attic
Интересно а у неё с чердаком всё было
you'll wash your wife not about
нормально ты помою жену не про
[laughter]
[смех]
this rude rude this is a very rude young
эту грубо грубо это очень грубой молодой
man then everything was fine with that friend's attic
человек то у той подруги с чердаком всё
No but
нормально Нет
How did your wife
а Как ваша жена с ней
introduce her to her How did you
познакомила Как вы
meet and your spouse you are with us and also
познакомились а супруга ты у нас а тоже
after the factory like us that is we with in general
после завода как мы то есть мы с вообще
after the Pokrovsky family Oh yeah by no You
же после Покровских род Ой да по не Ты
then got there
же потом попал
turn around I first worked at the factory
поворот Я сначала работал на заводе
then I got a job as a waitress in uh Yeah I
потом Я устроилась официанткой в э Ага я
worked there for about three months and I left here
проработала там месяца три и я ушла тут
ran away to through Viknu grandma yeah
сбежала в через через викну бабушку да
you got there yeah yeah And there I come and there
ты попала да да да И там я прихожу и там
yeah we would have worked in short you know VTsIOM you
бы да мы короче работали знаешь вциом
know such a Russian organization uh it
знаешь такую организацию российскую ээ
does polls Yes here we are yeah here we all
опросы делает Да вот мы да вот мы все
met there  roughly
там познакомились грубо
speaking that is we all work there I
говоря то есть мы там все работаем Я
know she was my neighbor and so yes that is
знаю она моя соседка была а так да то
yes They used to be neighbors on the
есть да Они раньше там соседками были на
same street it's
одной улице
cool in general it's a real
прикольно вообще вообще прям
tragedy Yes wait do I understand correctly
трагедия Да подожди я правильно понимаю
that you were eager to go to
что ты порывался пойти на
war to pay off the debts that your
войну крыть долги которые взяла твоя
wife took out for that friend who was hanging out with the drug addict Well
жена для этой подруги которая с нарком
and don't forget that they can't
Ну и не забывай что меня не
hear me What's okay Well don't you forget that she can't hear me Well your
слышат Что ладно Ну ты не забываешь что
wife can't hear you I can hear me she can't
меня она Ну супруга не слышит тебя я
hear you with she can hear me Yes yes yes you got it Yes I got it Yes that's
слышишь Да да
exactly it's some kind of TV series like not
именно это прям какой-то сериал типа не
I'm telling you right away you don't need to
я тебе сразу говорю оно тебе не нужно
go Because you know and there won't be any money
идти Потому что знаешь и бабок не будет
in short
короче
and at war and in short Oh that's why I'm
и на войне а Короче О так поэтому я
sitting with you now and talking and she'll
сейчас сижу с тобой и общаюсь а она
find someone in short you know in such an
найдёт какого-то короче ещё знаешь таким
attic So it's better not
чердаком Так что лучше не
exactly
на именно
yes you know women are fragile creatures and it's not
да знаешь женщины существа хрупкие и не
always this well you got it got it she beats you
всегда это ну ты понял понял она тебя
Well for the last 3 years
бьёт Ну последние 3 года
No you looked at her so scared no
Нет ты так перепуга на неё
just no I see What if he
посмотрел нет просто нет вижу А вдруг он
hears your question it became terribly scary
слышит твой вопрос страшно страшно стало
yes  No no no beats does not beat
да Да не не не бьёт не бьёт
What kind of
Что за
nervous and teeth who
нервничал а зубы кто
knocked out teeth Listen I have some falling out Understand
выбил зубы Слушай у меня насле выпадают
I
Поня Я
thought I
думал
needed a dentist
надо зубного
How many
Сколько
one understood And you have
один понял А у тебя есть
yes one four four
да один
four teeth not teeth
четверо четверо четыре зуба не зуба
four children I understood It's just she's
четверо детей я понял Это она просто
old heard and ask
старая услышала и спроси
no Three girls three
нет Три девчонки три
boys three boys Imagine at a
мальчика три мальчика Прикинь за
time not one is enough You see for a
раз не одного достаточно Вот видишь
wife one is enough We have T one and
супруге одного достаточно У нас Т один а
you and your wife what do you work as
вы с супругой кем работаете
now the wife is a
сейчас супруга
salesman And you And I what is the correct
продавец А вы А я как правильно
name of the
называется
chemical it turns out I MTZ MTZ manager of a
химикат получается я МТЗ МТЗ менеджер
store A yes rudely said not a salesman
торгового А да грубо сказал не продавец
manager of a store for forget We are still
менеджер торгового за забывай Мы ещё
learning what she can do Nastya here and I
учимся тому что умеет Настя вот а я
chemical understood And look except for
химикат понял А смотрите кроме
these loans for that friend no
этих кредитов для той подруги никакие
other loans were taken out there are none of your own So what did you
больше не брали кредиты нет своих-то Так
take for the horse said for all sorts of things there
а на что брали коне сказа на всяку там
somewhere something there a phone number no not some
гдето что-то там телефончик нене которые
unpaid Well ask your wife
не выплаченные А ну спросите у жены
Which of your unpaid loans
Какие из невыплаченных кредитов ваших
exactly does she still have Well here are yours your
именно есть ещё у неё Ну вот ваши вашей
wife Yes what loans do you have unpaid
жены Да какие кредиты у вас не выплачены
for
на
what Yes, everything is left credit card Yes 35 from
что Да всё кредитка осталась Да 35 из
Debts what else and how much is there
Долгов что ещё и сколько там
30 well he money there Wants to throw off said
30 ну он денег там Хочет скинет сказал
000 Now he will throw off this millions of dollars
000 Сейчас скинет это миллионов долларов
Yes of course it's very funny of course No well
Да конечно очень смешно конечно Не ну
how much is
сколько
there well 250 Yes
там ну 250 Да
300 I have 200 only
300 У меня 200 только кредит
one loan Well in short there is also a credit card there is another
один Ну короче там ещё кредитка там ещё
loan and I also have two more loans not so For
кредит и у меня также ещё два кредита не
what For what these loans I
так На что На что эти кредиты мне
wonder what we spent on click to drink on to go for a
интересно на что мы тратили нажать
walk No and
набухать на гулять Нет а
what these debts once howled
что эти долги раз выли
covered so let's say a break Well
перекрывали так скажем перерыва Ну
initially initially initially there
изначально изначально изначально там
even this loan which mine at 50 I
даже вот этот кредит который мой в 50 я
took so that you would cover your debts Well yes
брала чтобы ты закрывал долги свои Ну да
Basically overlapping closing
В основном перекрытие закрытие
overlapping and stop stop stop I
перекрытие а стоп стоп стоп Я правильно
understood correctly my wife took out a loan to close the
понял жена брала кредит чтобы закрыть
loan that
кредит который брали
you took not Hang out this is a very interesting
вы не Зависай это очень интересная
story I want to unpack it to the end to
история Я хочу распаковать её до конца
understand
понять
[music] the
[музыка]
loan for the Internet has
кредит на интернет
run out of credit limit Nantes
закончился кредитный лимит нанте
Well develop or
Ну разви снишь или
not
нет
everything yes So there in Russia yes on these
всё да Так там в России да на этих
microloans damn sits in short there are
микрозаймах блин сидит короче там
so many overdue payments  that's why they go to
просрочки столько он поэтому идут на
war you see Yes it's brutal
войну видите Да жесть
of course like squeak
конечно лайк писка
comment letter on y instag I don't know why it's for you why you should
комент пись на й instag Я не знаю для
watch on my
чого це тоб для чого тоб там дивитись на
face But for you it's one two
оце мий фейс Але для тебе це один два
or three clicks But you try me and I
або три клика Але ты тримае мене и я
'll say Wow I have a bunch of fouls and
буду казати Вау в мене там Купа фолов и
I'll be in a great mood to make
в мене буде класный настр чтоб робити
new cool video letter on my Instagram
нове крут видео пись на мий Instagram
Popik Andriy Oh
Попик Андрий О
so come on I'm
так давай я тебя
waiting for you E
чекаю E